- Hi, I'm
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Senator Mike Lee. Laborers of Utah started as an opportunity to celebrate Pioneer Day, the 24th of July, in Washington, D.C. We started by serving homemade root beer. Little by little, we got interest from Utah food producers and it turned into an opportunity to showcase
Food
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): produced in Utah to Washington DC has become known far and wide on both ends of the Capitol in both political
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): parties as one of the best events of the year to sample good food and its food from
Utah.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): I want to thank the Utah food producers who contributed to this year's event and made it possible for us.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): to donate these gift bags to our doctors, nurses, and first responders to every registered certified accredited hospital in the state. These are the men and women who are keeping us afloat,
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): keeping us going during the global pandemic and I thank them and all the food producers who participated.
To
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): the doctors, nurses, and first responders throughout our state, thank you for all you do. Thank you for keeping
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): us healthy. Thank you for keeping us safe and giving us the confidence that we need to move forward.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Hi, my name is Chris Bowler. I am the CEO of Creminelli Fine Meats. And Creminelli Fine Meats dry cures Italian charcuterie products like salami,
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): prosciutto and pancetta and other wonderful specialty food products of Italian origin and we do that right here in Salt Lake City, Utah. It's a unique year everything is a little bit different this year and we're glad that we're able to do something in celebration of Utah's food and it feels all the more meaningful to do it in celebration and in gratitude of our frontline workers.
Speaker 4: Hi, I'm Rowena Montoya, the owner of Julie Ann Carmel's. We make over 40 different
places
Speaker 4: flavors of caramel. We're a local company here in Salt Lake City, Utah. We use a local dairy. Our caramels are really fresh. There's no preservatives in it. We keep it really simple with five ingredients. Utah brings people together. You know, we are big into family. We love helping one another. You can't have a better cheerleader than someone in Utah.
- I'm
Speaker 5: Alan Lauer. - I'm Chad
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): Lauer. We represent Lauer Family Foods in Richmond, Utah.
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): you know we're in the cache valley which is a beautiful valley here nestled in the northern part of the state with you know gorgeous mountains and it's green and it's it's lush and it's it's beautiful but not just the beauty um in this valley and not just the valley of the state of utah i think there's a sense of community a sense of unity especially here recently with the challenges that we've all been struggling with with covid
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): 19 and the effects of that you know you kind of get the feeling that we're all in this together you know so we're we're not just a community a state we're a family and you know i feel that here in in the state of utah
Speaker 7: My name is Jason Glade. I'm the president
Speaker 8 (lower-pitched voice): CEO of Taffy Town Taffy Town is a fourth generation family business that makes saltwater taffy and We make the best in the country. We're proud of it
Speaker 8 (lower-pitched voice): We love the state of Utah. My great-grandfather started the business over 100 years ago here in the state and we fall in love with this state and what it does for us. We love the values the state brings, the family core values, the environment, the beauty of the scenery here in the state and it serves as a great crossroads for
Speaker 9: distribution, marketing and travel around the country.
Speaker 9: Dave Davis, president and
Speaker 10 (lower-pitched voice): CEO of the Utah Food Industry Association.
So I
Speaker 10 (lower-pitched voice): think it's more important this year to be involved than ever before. With the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic, it would have been really easy for
us and the
Speaker 10 (lower-pitched voice): the team to just fold up shop and say we're going to come back next year and do this but I think there was a strong feeling that we wanted to do something to give back to the community and so we feel like it's really important to be involved in rewarding and recognizing our medical first responders.
Speaker 10 (lower-pitched voice): We would extend our gratitude to those on the front lines of our medical facilities, those that are treating and attending to COVID-19 patients and are going out there and every day putting themselves at risk to serve their communities. I'm Scott
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): Anderson, President and CEO of Zions Bank.
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): and zions bank is the oldest banking operation in utah it's been around for almost 150 years and we are happy to be in this community i have the honor of being on the board of intermountain healthcare and so i see from that position
Speaker 11 (lower-pitched voice): the hours, the work, the risk, the doctors and nurses and all of the caregivers put themselves at. And they do it because they have compassion, they want to help people, and I appreciate that. And I want them to know that we all appreciate it and we all recognize it. So to all of you caregivers, thank you so much. And to Senator Lee, thank you for honoring them in this way.